Some Day Your Prince Will Come. A lusty, rowdy spoof
of all your favorite fairy tales!
Fairy Tales is a adventure, comedy, romance film directed by Harry Hurwitz.
On his twenty-first birthday, the Prince goes on a quest that takes him across the land
searching for the one woman that gets him sexually excited, Princess Sleeping Beauty.
Prince, played by Don Sparks.
Sirus, played by Sy Richardson.
Sleeping Beauty, played by Linnea Quigley.
Gussie Gander, played by Brenda Fogarty.
Doorman / Tommy Tucker, played by Robert Staats.
Dr. Eyes, played by Irwin Corey.
Fairy Tales, released in the UK as Adult Fairy Tales, is a 1978 sex comedy directed by
Harry Hurwitz, the plot of which revolves around the stereotypical fairy tale.
The film explores themes of fairy tale, musical, sex comedy.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.